Okay, everybody close your eyes.
Breathe in and breathe out.
Breathe in to this energy now and let the ball energy ball getting bigger and bigger
as you are breathing in and out into this energy ball.
Breathe in and breathe out.
Now focus.
Your focus is on this beautiful energy ball.
This energy ball is going down, down, down, down, down into the mother earth.
Using all the layers of the mother earth, it is reaching to the core of the mother earth,
which is very, very important.
There is a fire there.
Now you are marinating this ball and slowly gradually it is coming towards your feet
crossing all the layer of mother earth.
Through your feet, through your legs, through your spine, taking your Kundalini up.
The energy ball is now on the top of your head.
So now you will see one more beautiful energy ball coming through mother earth, cleansing
your entire body, each and every cell of the body.
It is again merging with the first one.
So you will see a very beautiful energy ball.
He having healing properties coming to your feet through mother earth and now after cleansing
your body, it is merging to the first one.
Now one more energy ball is coming, which is very, very beautiful.
It is also a beautiful healing divine ball.
Again, it is coming towards your feet, through your feet, through your legs, through your
spine.
Again, it is there with the other two balls.
You will see your spirit or your essence into this energy ball.
Now this energy ball is going up, up, up in the sky, crossing all the layers of the clouds.
It is going towards the universe.
You are entering into the universe.
The first thing you are seeing is all the planets.
You are seeing all the planets.
These are the energy of your own planets.
Look at them, enjoy the energy of the planets, seeing them.
Now you are seeing the layers of dark light bright light.
So dark light is just to separate two layers.
So there are many, many layers.
So you are crossing all the layers of the bright light dark light and you are reaching
to a jelly light substance where you have all the seven colors.
All the geometrical shapes.
Now you are looking for all the geometrical shapes.
Triangle hexagon octagon square rectangle circle star, gold pyramid.
All the shapes are there.
All the geometrical shapes.
Now you are looking for a paint.
You will be seeing off white light, but still it is sparking.
It is very shiny and it is reflecting seven colors which is very faded, but it is there.
So while you are going through this place, you are reaching to a place where there is
a window is opening which is seven planes window.
You are marinating yourself into this light, releasing all your tiredness, fatigue,
here as you want to be energetic.
Because today you are going to meet your in-laws and sisters.
Today you also want to meet you.
You are looking at them, all of them.
See how they are feeling while they see.
Are they angry?
Are they happy?
And you will see your life partner also there.
Your wife or your husband.
You will see your child is also there.
Whether you have one or two children.
You will see your family there.
Now please look at them and say that we are today here to meet you.
So you say greater of all that is, it is requested that let me see all my in-laws and
sister or not women one.
You will see huge number of your and sister from different families.
Look at your emotions and their emotions.
If you have any problem through your and sister, right now you can discuss with them.
Say I have this problem, whatever is your problem, express your problem.
If you are facing domination, you are facing disconnection to your partner, whatever your
problem is.
Tell them this is the problem which is not us, we know it very well.
But it is there.
In the family and we are not happy, we are not growing.
Tell them and we are you to solve this problem today.
And tell them if you are not going to solve it today, then they coming generation will
carry it.
Tell them you really love all of you, really love all of you.
And you are happy to see them and you really respect them.
And say that we are here to give unconditional love to all of you from our side.
Say creator of all that is, it is requested that we send unconditional love to all
my and sister through each and every cell of their body.
Thank you.
It is done.
See the unconditional love is pouring on each and every and sister of yours, your any
love and sister.
You will find a lot of discomfort in your body or any pattern which is popping up in your
mind right now, which is not yours, which is coming from ancestors.
So say that all of these problems, what I'm facing by physical mental emotional is spiritual.
It is coming from you.
We are holding them in our space because we are the next generation and the present generation
of yours.
It's not ours because it is very difficult for us to carry.
So we want you to take it back.
Give them back.
Now say that I know you all had a very difficult fate.
You have your own part of struggles, disappointments failures, diseases, illnesses.
I know, but this is not us.
It's yours.
So I am giving you back.
So that we can be free from all the burdens of the curses, oaths, vows, commitment of your
space, which is not us who created it, who taken it.
So I'm giving you back all the burden which I'm carrying.
I am giving you back with belongs to all of you.
If you all like it or not, I am claiming my birthright.
I have taken before all of this out of love and loyalty.
I am giving you back now.
Go down in front of them, release all the burden from your back, especially from a spine.
Say all your good deeds, bad deeds, we are giving you back.
We are taking back only whatever is mine or ours.
It's not us.
So you releasing all the burden with respect and giving them back.
As you know already, the whole are strong enough to take care of their own problems, their
own dispartments.
Their own unhealed issues, you are giving them back.
See your partner also by going down, your children also going down.
When you are feeling as you are giving burden back to them, you are feeling a different
energy in your body.
You are taking back only what is yours.
Now all of you all with family, you are turning back and you see all your ancestor on your
back.
And you request them, please bless us and see us kindly when we live our life to the fullest.
If you are in loss, in mother-in-law, father-in-law is not alive, then see them back of you.
And if they are alive, then see the father-in-law and mother-in-law behind your partner.
And you are the holding hand of your partner.
And through your partner, you are getting that blessing, that support, which you really
need today.
Slowly, gradually, you are feeling that you are full of support, you are secure, you have
blessings, happiness and joy.
Secretor, thank you for showing me this day where I can release my in-law's burden of
their karma, their deeds.
And I come back to my power now.
And you are seeing all your ancestor going to their path and you are going to your path.
Now, you are coming out from seventh plane, feeling very happy, lighter and blessed.
All the curses and everything you have released now.
You are coming out to the jelly-like substance from there, crossing all the layers of
the wildlife bright light, you are coming down, down, down from the universe and reaching
to the place where you can see all your planets.
Now crossing all the layers of clouds coming down, down, down, down to the mother earth.
Now you will see the energy ball above your head.
Now, this energy ball is going down, down, down through your feet, crossing all the
layers of mother earth, it is there on the core of the mother earth.
You are seeing energy from there, it is coming out, out, out, out, and now this ball
is coming up and now you see this ball on the above of your head.
you can come back now.
[BLANK_AUDIO]